photocrati.com 2016-11-26

# Privacy Policy

### For Visitors and Readers (non-Customers)

Our log files store details such as your IP address, your browser type and the referring page and time of your visit. The information gathered is used only to enhance your experience when using our website.

We may use Cookies to remember your preferences when interacting with our website. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

We will contact you only if you have requested us to do so or if you have requested to be informed of updates to our site, in which case we will keep your name and email address in order to carry out your request.

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### For Customers

We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address or credit card information.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology (secured by Verisign) and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.photocrati.com/terms-conditions/.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, http://www.photocrati.com makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

http://www.photocrati.com uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

### **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

→ Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://www.photocrati.com.

→ Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to http://www.photocrati.com and other sites on the Internet.

→ Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

### Our Advertising Partners

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….

  * Google
  * Amazon
  * ShareASale
  * iDevAffiliate
  * eJunkie
  * onOne Software
  * EventEspresso
  * Bluehost
  * Dreamhost
  * WPMU
  * MCP Actions
  * Sucuri
  * SlideDeck

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on http://www.photocrati.com and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

http://www.photocrati.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

### **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there.  
This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using our Contact page.

**Update**  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Monday, March 25th, 2013.
